RENAN SOUZA

❖ (415) 505-2622 ❖ renanbarbosadesouza@gmail.com ❖ GitHub ❖ Linkedin

SKILLS

- Ruby
- JavaScript (Ajax, jQuery)
- ❖ Sinatra
- * Ruby on Rails
- ❖ PostgreSQL
- * HTML
- CSS
- SQLite
- ❖ Git and GitHub
- **❖** Teamwork
- ❖ Test Driven Development
- Project Management

PROJECTS

- **❖** Invisible Thread
- Grocery API (In Progress)
- Movie Review (In Progress)
- Checkers(Game) (In Progress)

OBJECTIVE

Seeking to apply my diverse experience and skill set in a position that offers new challenges and opportunity for growth

CERTIFICATIONS

Developer (2016)

Dev Bootcamp is a 19-week intensive training program for web developers, rooted in learning full stack development skills and empathetic team cooperation.

The technical program specializes in Ruby, JavaScript, SQL, HTML and CSS, and emphasizes big picture application and design practices such as OO programming, MVC architecture, and test-driven development.

EXPERIENCE

Printing Assistant, 2014 - 2016

The Blow Up Lab - San Francisco, CA

- Printed and mounted artwork, banners and murals.
- Learned Photoshop
- Digital printing and graphics

Inventory Management Consultant, 2013 - 2014

Mistura Fina - Salvador, Brazil

- ❖ Find problems in the inventory system and fix the problems.
- ❖ Teach how to keep the inventory system working properly

Receptionist, 2012 - 2013

Pousada Manga Rosa - Salvador, Brazil

- Checkins and Checkouts of guests
- Explain to the guest what they could do to have fun in the city and to keep themselves safe

Buyer and Inventory Maneger, 2011 - 2012

Munik - Salvador, Brazil

- ❖ Search for good quality products to supply the restaurant needs.
- Controlling the inventory flow

Waiter, 2007 - 2011

Portal do Mar - Salvador Brazil

- Make sure that the clients had a good time and were convicted that would came back
- Attend English and Spanish speakers
- Twice a week also being the supervisor

EDUCATION

Dev Bootcamp

Full Stack Developer (2016)

UNIFACS

Information and Technology (2013)